Oh, yeah!
I knew it! I knew it.
Kevin! As soon as
I heard that wrapper.
You really have
to say, "Oh, yeah,"
every time you
eat a candy bar?
I can't help it, Oscar.
It's just really good.
Oh, yeah!
My hands are tied.
All right, not bad at all.
I think we can beat 20 minutes,
though, so let's try again.
Get it all out
now if you have to.
It was a raccoon eating a
hamburger like a person.
You need to stop banging
your pen on your desk,
or it's gonna drive me insane.
Okay, got it.
Does anyone have
a first-aid kit?
Check out
this song I wrote.
I'm gonna love you
downstairs tonight
Listen, I say...
I mean, he looked
like a little Hamburglar.
All right, here we go!
Everybody, get ready in three, two...
Good luck. One.
Love letters.
Yes, I love it.
What else can be
done with paper?
You can write
a book about chairs.
Books. Excellent, Jim.
All right, Andy,
please, please, just stop.
You can do infinite things with paper.
Did you hear that?
Infinity. There is an infinity of
things that you can do with paper.
Now, who wants
to buy some paper?
Yeah!
Very nice.
Very nice sales pitch
for our clients that
don't know what paper is.
I'm talking about you guys.
Who in this room right now
wants to buy some paper?
Let's get high
on our own supply.
Andy, you want us
to buy our own paper?
Yes.
Robert said that we needed to
double our sales growth to 8%
by the end of the quarter. That's
today, and we are $830 short.
And I can't afford
to keep buying paper from us,
so today we need to
sell $830 of paper,
and then next quarter,
I need to sell
the $2,200 of paper
that's in my garage.
Animals, machines,
vast virtual armies.
All of these things
I have successfully managed.
The only thing I
haven't managed is people.
I saw an ad on
the Sabre website
for an open manager position
in their printers division.
I spoke to Robert
California about it,
and he said for me to come by
and see him some time.
So like
a Spanish conquistador,
I have come to Florida to claim
what is rightfully mine.
Dwight Schrute for
Robert California.
Oh. Hello, Mr. Schrute. I'll tell him you're here.
Can I get you anything at all?
I'm not here to
be given anything.
I'm here to take
what is mine.
Ooh. I'm glad you're on our team.
Here, please have a seat.
Dwight?
What are you doing here?
Gabe. You don't know?
Of course I know.
Hmm. Impressive
office you have here.
Surrounded by shrubbery.
Like a squirrel's office.
Corporate says to me, "Gabe,
we need you in Scranton."
Scranton says,
"Gabe, go back down
to Florida.
You're needed there."
So Tuesdays and Thursdays,
I'm up there.
Mondays, Wednesdays and
Fridays, I'm down here.
I can think of no better way to
confront my deathly fear of flying.
Dwight
Robert.
You made it.
Yes.
Impressive initiative.
I don't know what's worse,
the trip or the destination.
Well, let me settle in.
And I'll be with you shortly.
Very good.
Hey, C-SPAN.
So my Dad says an accountant
can really help you out
if they're willing to play ball.
Those were his words.
Gosh, Andy, you had
a great quarter, okay?
Robert will understand.
$800 is a rounding error.
So make that error.
Andy, no.
Hey,I can make that error. Oh...
Well, it's just I know that making
errors sounds like your kind of thing,
but it's a little more
complicated than that. No, I...
It's just I really need
a real accountant on this.
What do you say?
I am leaving early today,
because tonight I have a trivia
contest in Philadelphia.
Aw...
Any other crunch time,
I would love
to stay and cook
the books for you
so you can save face
in front of your CEO,
but tonight is Triviacolypse.
What?
It's only the biggest night
of trivia of the year.
There's a $1,000 prize.
I'm committed to my friends.
They're committed to me.
You know what? Go. Have fun.
There's a trivia contest
at a bar in Philadelphia.
Stop right there. I love it.
I'm in.
I didn't even say what it is.
It's trivia.
In Philadelphia.
But here's the best part.
The prize is $1,000,
and if we win, we can use
that money to buy paper here,
close the gap on our
8% profit increase.
That's a great idea. Yeah.
That's a great plan.
Yeah? You like it? All right.
All right, good stuff.
I'm so psyched you guys are
into it, 'cause I thought...
I was like,
"This sounds really stupid."
You just made a good idea,
a great idea.
There is one problem with this plan.
What?
We'd have to leave work,
like, right now to do this.
You can reduce
your prices by 10%,
or we're gonna be finding a new
source for our morning bagels.
All right.
Gabe, I always wondered what
it is you did around here.
Now I found out.
You're the bagel guy.
Yeah, but not just bagels.
All unwanted problems.
Question. What's the most important
appliance in your house?
Meat grinder.  Too slow.
It's the toilet.
And I am the toilet
of this office.
I flush away
annoying problems,
so others can keep
their hands clean,
and just like a toilet,
I am essential.
You know, Gabe,
you could have gone
with garbage disposal,
incinerator, or eraser.
And instead
you chose toilet.
God bless you.
You are an American classic.
Dwight, today is not my
day at all, I'm afraid.
I'm not going to be
able to meet with you.
But I'm leaving you in the
very capable hands of our COO.
But I can give you
this pitch in one minute.
He's gonna meet
with you later.
No,no,no. I don't
want you to rush it, okay?
Trust me. Meet with Bill.
He's a great person to know.
I'll dialog with him tonight.
CEO to COO. What a
difference a letter makes.
Still an important position.
Still a chief.
You're really
going to like Bill.
He has me toilet
a lot of people for him.
Hallway phone.
Gabe Lewis speaking.
Gabe, listen to me.
Don't bother Bill with this.
He needs to go put out a fire
on the home front.
Just wait 20 minutes, and then I want
you to listen to Dwight's pitch.
Make him feel valued.
Make him feel heard.
Your wish is my command.
It's a command.
I don't believe this.
What are you doing here, Andy?
You left us no choice.
But this should put
a smile on your face.
How would you like to be captain
of the Dunder Mifflin team?
Although I reserve the right
to overrule you. What? No.
I got a quota to hit.
I don't care how I hit it.
And you guys thought
this was a good idea?
I thought it was
a fun idea.
There were times on the two and a half
hour drive when I experienced doubt.
But that's the thing
about long drives,
you know?
You're always going...
This is a gay bar.
Wait, what?
Everyone in here is gay?
Yes. It's a gay bar, so you
guys want to go home now?
No.
Awesome.
What does this say about you
that you followed me here?
That you think
you're going to win
your sales quota at
a gay bar's trivia night?
It says that I believe
in my staff's intelligence,
and that I'm
willing to try anything.
Not "anything."
Good luck.
All right, we need to
divide up into teams,
but it's winner take all,
so no need to divide evenly.
We need an A team, a backup
team, and a just-have-fun team.
So you guys all
know yourselves.
Good timers, follow me.
Back-ups.
Go on, kid. You know
you don't belong here.
A team.
Okay.
All right, everybody,
nice self awareness.
Except...
Okay.
There's a table over here.
All right,
first question, everyone.
Ray Charles famously had
this state on his mind.
What is its capital?
Oh, we got this.
Let's reverse engineer this.
You're a black singer.
Where do you go?
Somewhere where
you're a novelty.
Alaska.
Atlanta.
I know you think that, because
that's where the Olympics were held.
My cousins were
actually at those Olympics.
Keep talking all you want.
How am I supposed to know
what was on his mind?
Ooh! What do blind
people think about?
Okay, dogs, canes, signs, manholes,
stairs, piano, darkness.
Okay, time's up.
Let's get the boards up.
Atlanta, Georgia is
the correct answer.
What?
Hey, man. Uh...
Look, unfortunately,
Bill had to go fight a fire,
so, your appointment got...
There's no fires
within eight miles of here.
Well, it's nine miles away.
I'm going to be meeting
with you on his behalf.
What? No, no.
Excuse me, lady!
Get anyone from the COO's office
on the phone this instant!
This must be
very frustrating.
I can see you in
the jungle now.
Hey, now, you're not an All-Star of
the NBA, but you did get your game on
when you won the NBA 's Sixth
Man of the Year Award in 2011.
Who are you?
Jim, Darryl,
your time to shine.
Shawn Marion.
Yes. Shawn Marion.
That doesn't sound right. I want
to say LaDamien Washington?
Wrong for so many reasons.
Well, I know
Elizabeth Taylor's sixth man
was Richard Burton.
Is that helpful?
That's it. I'm gonna go watch
the boats on the river.
Ron Artest, Kelly.
No, it's Lamar Odom.
If it had been Ron Artest,
it would have
come up on
Dancing with the Stars
when they pan
over his trophy case
when he's at home
with his family.
Lamar winning Sixth Man was a big
storyline on Khloé and Lamar.
All right, boards up.
Let's see who got it.
Lamar Odom is what
we were looking for.
Lamar Odom.
Oh, my God,
Nice. Nicely done.
You're my sports guys. You're ESPN.
You're ESPN Classic.
Ryan is MSNBC.
I'm El, TLC and Oxygen.
Chill, man.
This plan is airtight.
So it's a very
simple argument
of why I should be put in charge
of southeast printer sales.
Nobody has sold more printers
in the northeast than me.
Bottom line, I know the product.
I get it.
Well, you got my vote.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Most of all, I believe
that character is destiny,
and my character
is one that...
Wait, why are you smiling?
What?
What's with the smile?
You're doing great.
So good.
And my character is one
that will never give up
until greatness is on
the horizon behind us.
Dwight, that was a fantastic presentation.
Put your hand on my hand.
Flush.
Ow!
Take me to Robert.
Ow. He went home.
Take me to his house.
It's a condo.
It's long-term
business housing.
You know where it is.
Lead me there.
Ow. Stephanie, help.
Listen, you're
a perfectly fine toilet.
I'm just an extraordinary
piece of crap. Let's go.
Ow.
Excuse me, sir,
on the Dunder Mifflin A team.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah?
I'm sure you're just checking
your Grindr account.
But you can't
check smartphones
during trivia.
It's against the rules.
Okay, I'm turning it off.
Okay, you're not
turning it off.
I won't look at it.
Sir.
I can't not touch it.
Okay, then we're gonna
have to take it away.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, I can't not
have my phone. I'm sorry.
I want to be with my phone.
All right, guys, after nine
rounds, let's check the scores.
In first place with nine
points, it's Aesop's Foibles.
The Queerenstein
Bears have seven points.
Dunder Mifflin
A team has four points.
All right.
The D.M. Backup Team
has three points.
The Einsteins have eight points.
Ladies Gaga have five points.
Yeah!
So our best chance
of hitting our mark
is now in the hands and brains of
Kevin, Meredith, Erin and Kelly.
Do I like these odds?
My answer is no.
Whoo!
Which one is it? I don't know!
All I know is the building.
Robert! Robert California!
Dwight
Robert!
How nice of Gabe to
show you where I live.
Come around. 102.
All right, guys, time's up.
Who was the relatively
unknown patent clerk
who discovered
that energy equals
mass times
the speed of light squared?
Looks like everyone gets a
point for Albert Einstein.
Wait, except
for the Einsteins.
That's all right.
Which means
the top three teams
are going to finish it
off in the speed round.
So let's get
everyone some bells.
In third place,
we have the Einsteins.
Oh, yeah!
What?
Second place, we have
the Queerenstein Bears.
Yeah!
Come on!
And first place
is Aesop's Foibles.
Whoo!
Yeah, but they're
going to get clobbered.
Ring it in when you know it.
First question.
This man had a fatwa
declared on him when...
Einsteins?
What?
What is it?
I did my part, babe.
I'm just the bell girl.
Aesop's?
Salman Rushdie.
Salman Rushdie is correct.
Heading out to sea, sailors.
On a square-rigged
ship, the sail
set furthest
forward is called what?
Princess Ding-Dong,
do not hit that bell...
Flying jib.
Flying jib is
correct for the Einsteins.
Flying jib. Flying jib.
No Way.
Gentlemen.
Give us just a minute. Stew and I
are just finishing up our lesson.
Trust me,
one nine-minute bout
is a cardiovascular equivalent of
running uphill for three hours.
I could go to
the gym three times a week,
or I can wrestle
Stew once a month.
Grab my leg!
Yay, Robert!
Guys, please help yourself to
some drinks from the fridge.
According to a recent survey,
this is the most common learning
disability among American adolescents.
Boom! ADHD.
No.
Wrong. The
answer is dyslexia!
That's correct
for the Einsteins.
All right.
Whoo! Yeah!
Sir, sir. Dial it back. This
isn't Tail Feathers, okay?
Yeah!
They haven't really improved
on the Oreo, have they?
No, thank you.
Sit down, Dwight.
Let me tell you
why I should be
the next manager
with a riddle.
A manager,
a salesman, a leader
and a warrior walk
into a restaurant.
The hostess says,
"Table for one?"
How is this possible?
You were dining alone.
All those people are you.
Yes. Exactly. Riddle number two.
Who is going...
Your drive, your ambition, it would
be wasted on a manager's job.
And Florida,
you don't want to live here.
Even I don't
want to live here.
It's why I'm always at
my place in Scranton.
Florida is America's basement.
It's wet. It's filled with mold,
strange insects, alligators.
Alligators are dinosaurs, Dwight.
You know that, right?
Eh... It's complicated.
This medal was
my grandfather's.
He received it for acts of
courage, for excellence.
It's a tribute
one man gives another.
I could give you
a job, Dwight.
But why not let me give you
something even better?
It's a job interview.
Not a flea market.
Dwight, the job is
not right for you.
Now, when something
comes along
that is right for you,
I'll try you out.
Now get the hell
out of my place.
Yes.
Final round.
Last two teams squaring off.
I hope you're
ready to play doctor.
Our question is about
health and the human body.
Oh, come on.
The standard
American analog scale
has a maximum capacity of what weight?
Three hundred pounds.
Point for the Einsteins.
Here's your final question. Cinephiles,
put on your memory berets.
This 2001 masterpiece
from Gilles Paquet-Brenner
explores the intricate dynamics
of a family in disarray.
Yes!
I'm sorry, no.
Over to the Einsteins.
- Les Jolies Choses.
- Are you sure?
Marion Cotillard
exposes herself
a number of times
in that film.
The Einsteins win it.
No!
Yeah!
Come on!
Look, I know it's easy to say
tonight was just a fluke,
and maybe it was,
but here's a piece of trivia.
A fluke is one of the most
common fish in the sea.
So if you go
fishing for a fluke,
chances are you
just might catch one.
Oh, boy.
Welcome to the Stonewall
Alliance Trivia Championships!
First prize is $2,500.
Let's just do our thing, collect our
hardware, and get the hell home.
Whoo!
Riboflavin.
Riboflavin?
Michigan.
The President of
the United States
is POTUS.
John Steinbeck wrote
The Grapes of Wrath.